{
    "id": "182795d17a2a438ea49724feb6a1ae27",
    "title": "While And During",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I met a nice French girl ……………….. my stay in Switzerland.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "while",
                "during"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "……………… I was holidaying in Switzerland, I met a nice French girl.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "While",
                "During"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I learned some Russian ………………. I was studying in Russia.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "while",
                "during"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We can meet ………………. lunchtime.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "during",
                "while"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "It happened ………………. I was working in the garden.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "while",
                "during"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I was in hospital ………………… the winter.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "while",
                "during"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The shop was closed ……………….. the whole of March.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "during",
                "while"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I had some strange experiences ………………. working in France.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "while",
                "during"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I woke up ……………….. the night.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "while",
                "during"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I cooked dinner ………………. Samuel watched TV.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "during",
                "while"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}